Guide to the Cecily Brownstone Papers MSS.134
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Author Files
  - Hartman, Catherine, undated (Box 2, Folder 339)
  - Hartmett, Mary, undated (Box 2, Folder 340)
  - Harvey, Peggy, undated (Box 2, Folder 341)
  - Harwood, Trish, undated (Box 2, Folder 342)
  - Hawkins, Margaret, undated (Box 2, Folder 343)
  - Hayes, Irene, undated (Box 2, Folder 344)
  - Hazelton, Nika, undated (Box 2, Folder 345)
  - Heatter, Maida, undated (Box 2, Folder 346)
  - Heavenhill, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 347)
  - Heller, Edna, undated (Box 2, Folder 348)
  - Helmer, Howard and Joan O'Sullivan, undated (Box 2, Folder 349)
  - Hemingway, Mary, undated (Box 2, Folder 350)
  - Henderson, Louise, undated (Box 2, Folder 351)
  - Herbert, Jack, undated (Box 2, Folder 352)
  - Háriteau, Jacqueline, undated (Box 2, Folder 353)
  - Herman, Barry, undated (Box 2, Folder 354)
  - Herrmann, Martin, undated (Box 2, Folder 355)
  - Hershey's Chocolate, undated (Box 2, Folder 356)
  - Hess, Karen, undated (Box 2, Folder 357)
  - Heth, Edward, undated (Box 2, Folder 358)
  - Hewitt, Jean, undated (Box 2, Folder 359)
  - Hieatt, Constance and Sharon Butler, undated (Box 2, Folder 360)
  - Hill, Sallie, undated (Box 2, Folder 361)
  - Hillman, James, undated (Box 2, Folder 362)
  - Hillman, Libby, undated (Box 2, Folder 363)
  - Hines, Duncan, undated (Box 2, Folder 364)
  - Hodgson, Marion, undated (Box 2, Folder 365)
  - Hodgson, Moira, undated (Box 2, Folder 366)
  - Hoffman, Willa, undated (Box 2, Folder 367)
  - Hoge, Tom, undated (Box 2, Folder 368)
  - Holberg, Ruth, undated (Box 2, Folder 369)
  - Holt, Geraldene, undated (Box 2, Folder 370)
  - Hopkins, Roger, undated (Box 2, Folder 371)
  - Horowitz, Ruth, undated (Box 2, Folder 372)
  - Horton, Lucy, undated (Box 2, Folder 373)
  - House and Garden, undated (Box 2, Folder 374)
  - Howard, Bill, undated (Box 2, Folder 375)
  - Howard, Maria, undated (Box 2, Folder 376)
  - Howse, Ruth, undated (Box 2, Folder 377)
  - Hoyt, Robert, undated (Box 2, Folder 378)
  - Hume, Rosemary, undated (Box 2, Folder 379)
  - Hunt, Peter, undated (Box 2, Folder 380)
  - Hunter, Beatrice, undated (Box 2, Folder 381)
  - Hunter, Elizabeth, undated (Box 2, Folder 382)
  - Hunter, Pat, undated (Box 2, Folder 383)
  - Huxley, Judith, undated (Box 2, Folder 384)
  - Idone, Christopher, undated (Box 2, Folder 385)
  - Innes, Jocasta, undated (Box 2, Folder 386)
  - Irwin, May, undated (Box 2, Folder 387)
  - Jackson, Edwina, undated (Box 2, Folder 388)
  - Jacobson, Nora, undated (Box 2, Folder 389)
  - Jaffrey, Madhur, undated (Box 2, Folder 390)
  - James, Philip, undated (Box 2, Folder 391)
  - Jarratt, Enrica and Vernon, undated (Box 2, Folder 392)
  - Johnson, Hugh and James Halliday, undated (Box 2, Folder 393)
  - Johnson, Jackie, undated (Box 2, Folder 394)
  - Johnson, Myrna, undated (Box 2, Folder 395)
  - Johnson, Ray et al, undated (Box 2, Folder 396)
  - Jolliffe, Norman, undated (Box 2, Folder 397)
  - Jones, Evan and Judith, undated (Box 2, Folder 398)
  - Jones, Helen, undated (Box 2, Folder 399)
  - Jones, Jeanne, undated (Box 2, Folder 400)
  - Jones, Judith, undated (Box 2, Folder 401)
  - Jones, Suzanne, undated (Box 2, Folder 402)
  - Jones, Will, undated (Box 2, Folder 403)
  - Jordan, Sara, undated (Box 2, Folder 404)
  - Jorgensen, Claire, undated (Box 2, Folder 405)
  - Judell, Debra, undated (Box 2, Folder 406)
  - Julian, Noah, undated (Box 2, Folder 407)
  - Junior League of Jackson, undated (Box 2, Folder 408)
  - Junior League of New Orleans, undated (Box 2, Folder 409)
  - Junior League of Palo Alto, undated (Box 2, Folder 410)
  - Junior League of Pasadena, undated (Box 2, Folder 411)
  - Junior League of Winston-Salem, undated (Box 2, Folder 412)
  - Kafka, Barbara, undated (Box 2, Folder 413)
  - Käkönen-Anobile, Ulla, undated (Box 2, Folder 414)
  - Kander, Lizzie Black, undated (Box 2, Folder 415)
  - Kaplan, Dorothy, undated (Box 2, Folder 416)
  - Kardon, James, undated (Box 2, Folder 417)
  - Kasdan, Sara, undated (Box 2, Folder 418)
  - Kasin, Miriam, undated (Box 2, Folder 419)
  - Katims, Milton, undated (Box 2, Folder 420)
  - Katzenbach, Lois and William, undated (Box 2, Folder 421)
  - Kaufman, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 422)
  - Kavasch, Barrie, undated (Box 2, Folder 423)
  - Kaye, Sylvia, undated (Box 2, Folder 424)
  - Keegan, Marcia, undated (Box 2, Folder 425)
  - Kelly, Grace, undated (Box 2, Folder 426)
  - Kerle, Claire, undated (Box 2, Folder 427)
  - Kerr, W. Park, undated (Box 2, Folder 428)
  - Kerrigan, Janet, undated (Box 2, Folder 429)
  - Keyes, Frances, undated (Box 2, Folder 430)
  - Keys, Ancel and Margaret, undated (Box 2, Folder 431)
  - Kiene, Julia, undated (Box 2, Folder 432)
  - Kimball, Marie, undated (Box 2, Folder 433)
  - Kimball, Yeffe and Jean Anderson, undated (Box 2, Folder 434)
  - Kinsella, Susan, undated (Box 2, Folder 435)
  - Kirschenbaum, Grace, undated (Box 2, Folder 436)
  - Kleeman, Elayne and Jeanne Voltz, undated (Box 2, Folder 437)
  - Klein, Matthew, undated (Box 2, Folder 438)
  - Kluger, Marilyn, undated (Box 2, Folder 439)
  - Knopf, Mildred, undated (Box 2, Folder 440)
  - Kolpas, Norman, undated (Box 2, Folder 441)
  - Koock, Mary, undated (Box 2, Folder 442)
  - Krescholleck, Margie, undated (Box 2, Folder 443)
  - Krieg, Saul, undated (Box 2, Folder 444)
  - Kup, Karl, undated (Box 2, Folder 445)
  - Kutas, Richard, undated (Box 2, Folder 446)
  - Kweder, David, undated (Box 2, Folder 447)
  - Lamb, Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 448)
  - Land, Mary, undated (Box 2, Folder 449)
  - Lane, Carolyn and Pamela Zapata, undated (Box 2, Folder 450)
  - Lang, George, undated (Box 2, Folder 451)
  - Langseth-Christensen, Lillian, undated (Box 2, Folder 452)
  - Lansky, Vicki, undated (Box 2, Folder 453)
  - LaPrade, Malcolm, undated (Box 2, Folder 454)
  - Larousse, Pierre, undated (Box 3, Folder 455)
  - Laverty, Maura, undated (Box 3, Folder 456)
  - Law, Emma, undated (Box 3, Folder 457)
  - Lawson, Donna and Jean Coulon, undated (Box 3, Folder 458)
  - Layton, Miriam et al, undated (Box 3, Folder 459)
  - Leavitt, Sophie, undated (Box 3, Folder 460)
  - Lederman, Ann, undated (Box 3, Folder 461)
  - Lee, Calvin, undated (Box 3, Folder 462)
  - Lee, Dorothy, undated (Box 3, Folder 463)
  - Lee, Harvey, undated (Box 3, Folder 464)
  - Lee, Nata, undated (Box 3, Folder 465)
  - Lehr, Lew, undated (Box 3, Folder 466)
  - Leighton, Frances, undated (Box 3, Folder 467)
  - Leinwand, Rita, undated (Box 3, Folder 468)
  - Leinwoll, Stanley, undated (Box 3, Folder 469)
  - Lemieux, Joanne, undated (Box 3, Folder 470)
  - Lemlin, Jeanne, undated (Box 3, Folder 471)
  - Leonard, Leah, undated (Box 3, Folder 472)
  - Lerner, Anne, undated (Box 3, Folder 473)
  - Lescarboura, Louis, undated (Box 3, Folder 474)
  - Lesem, Jeanne, undated (Box 3, Folder 475)
  - Leslie, Eliza, undated (Box 3, Folder 476)
  - Leverton, Ruth, undated (Box 3, Folder 477)
  - Levine, Lois, undated (Box 3, Folder 478)
  - Levinson, Leonard, undated (Box 3, Folder 479)
  - Levy, Faye, undated (Box 3, Folder 480)
  - Lian, Vivien, undated (Box 3, Folder 481)
  - Lichine, Alexis, undated (Box 3, Folder 482)
  - Lin, Florence, undated (Box 3, Folder 483)
  - Lindquist, Carol, undated (Box 3, Folder 484)
  - Lincoln, D.A. [Mary Johnson Bailey], undated (Box 3, Folder 485)
  - Lindsey, Anne, undated (Box 3, Folder 486)
  - Liotto, Donna and Wendy Harris, undated (Box 3, Folder 487)
  - Lirio, Jack, undated (Box 3, Folder 488)
  - London, Bonne Rae, undated (Box 3, Folder 489)
  - Longone, Jan, undated (Box 3, Folder 490)
  - Lott, Arnold, undated (Box 3, Folder 491)
  - Lowell, Florence and Norma Lee Browning, undated (Box 3, Folder 492)
  - Lowenstein, Eleanor, undated (Box 3, Folder 493)
  - Lucas, Dione, undated (Box 3, Folder 494)
  - Lüchow, August, undated (Box 3, Folder 495)
  - Lyon, Romaine, undated (Box 3, Folder 496)
  - McBride, Mary, undated (Box 3, Folder 497)
  - McCall's, undated (Box 3, Folder 498)
  - McClure, Jon, undated (Box 3, Folder 499)
  - McCollum, Oscar [Mrs.], undated (Box 3, Folder 500)
  - McCoy, Elin and John Walker, undated (Box 3, Folder 501)
  - McCully, Helen, undated (Box 3, Folder 502)
  - McDonald, Barbara, undated (Box 3, Folder 503)
  - McDonald, Virginia, undated (Box 3, Folder 504)
  - McDouall, Robin, undated (Box 3, Folder 505)
  - McElyea, Jane, undated (Box 3, Folder 506)
  - McFee, Inez, undated (Box 3, Folder 507)
  - McGoldrick, Sherry, undated (Box 3, Folder 508)
  - McGrady, Mike, undated (Box 3, Folder 509)
  - Machlin, Edda, undated (Box 3, Folder 510)
  - McHugh, David, undated (Box 3, Folder 511)
  - McHugh, Gretchen, undated (Box 3, Folder 512)
  - McKendry, Maxime, undated (Box 3, Folder 513)
  - McLachlin, Jessica, undated (Box 3, Folder 514)
  - McMahan, Jacqueline, undated (Box 3, Folder 515)
  - Rand McNally and Co., undated (Box 3, Folder 516)
  - McNamara, Charlotte and Lenore Howell, undated (Box 3, Folder 517)
  - MacNeil, Karen, undated (Box 3, Folder 518)
  - Madden, Chris, undated (Box 3, Folder 519)
  - Magida, Phylis, undated (Box 3, Folder 520)
  - Mandel, Abby, undated (Box 3, Folder 521)
  - Manders, Olga, undated (Box 3, Folder 522)
  - Mann, Jim, undated (Box 3, Folder 523)
  - Manners, David, undated (Box 3, Folder 524)
  - Marcus, Adrianne, undated (Box 3, Folder 525)
  - Mares, William, undated (Box 3, Folder 526)
  - Marks, Copeland, undated (Box 3, Folder 527)
  - Marshall, Agnes, undated (Box 3, Folder 528)
  - Marshall, Lydie, undated (Box 3, Folder 529)
  - Marshall, Mel, undated (Box 3, Folder 530)
  - Martin, Faye, undated (Box 3, Folder 531)
  - Martin, Jeanne, undated (Box 3, Folder 532)
  - Marton, Beryl, undated (Box 3, Folder 533)
  - Matteson, Marilee, undated (Box 3, Folder 534)
  - Matthews, Joanne, undated (Box 3, Folder 535)
  - Maxwell, W. L. - The Church of Jesus Christ of the Latter-Day Saints, undated (Box 3, Folder 535 A)
  - Mayabb, Jim, undated (Box 3, Folder 536)
  - Mayer, [_____], undated (Box 3, Folder 537)
  - Maynard, Chris and Bill Scheller, undated (Box 3, Folder 538)
  - Mazza, Irma, undated (Box 3, Folder 539)
  - Meade, Martha, undated (Box 3, Folder 540)
  - Melikian, K. Cyrus, undated (Box 3, Folder 541)
  - Mendelson, Anne, undated (Box 3, Folder 542)
  - Merriman, Beth, undated (Box 3, Folder 543)
  - Meyer, Hazel, undated (Box 3, Folder 544)
  - Michalson, Bonni, undated (Box 3, Folder 545)
  - Michigan United Conservation Club, undated (Box 3, Folder 546)
  - Miller, Carey, undated (Box 3, Folder 547)
  - Miller, Lindsey, undated (Box 3, Folder 548)
  - Miloradovich, Milo, undated (Box 3, Folder 549)
  - Minnigerode, Meade, undated (Box 3, Folder 550)
  - Minster, [___] and Rafuse, [___], undated (Box 3, Folder 551)
  - Mitchell, Jan, undated (Box 3, Folder 552)
  - Mitchell, Marge and Joan Sedgwick, undated (Box 3, Folder 553)
  - Mitchell, Paulette, undated (Box 3, Folder 554)
  - Molinari, Lucille, undated (Box 3, Folder 555)
  - Moore, Alma, undated (Box 3, Folder 556)
  - Moore, Carolyn et al, undated (Box 3, Folder 557)
  - Moore, Eva, undated (Box 3, Folder 558)
  - Moore, Genie, undated (Box 3, Folder 559)
  - Moore-Betty, Maurice, undated (Box 3, Folder 560)
  - Moosewood, undated (Box 3, Folder 561)
  - Morash, Marian, undated (Box 3, Folder 562)
  - Morcrette, Daniel, undated (Box 3, Folder 563)
  - Morgan, Jan, undated (Box 3, Folder 564)
  - Morton, Marcia, undated (Box 3, Folder 565)
  - Morimoto, Jane, undated (Box 3, Folder 566)
  - Morse, Theresa, undated (Box 3, Folder 567)
  - Munn, David, undated (Box 3, Folder 568)
  - Murphy, Patricia, undated (Box 3, Folder 569)
  - Myers, Barbara, undated (Box 3, Folder 570)
  - Nash, Helen, undated (Box 3, Folder 571)
  - Nathan, Joan, undated (Box 3, Folder 572)
  - Nathan's Famous, Inc., undated (Box 3, Folder 573)
  - National Chicken Cooking Contest, undated (Box 3, Folder 574)
  - National Park Service, undated (Box 3, Folder 575)
  - Neal, Bill, undated (Box 3, Folder 576)
  - Nelson, Kay, undated (Box 3, Folder 577)
  - Nemiro, Beverly, undated (Box 3, Folder 578)
  - Nesbitt, Henrietta, undated (Box 3, Folder 579)
  - Ness, Joanne and Genell Subak-Sharpe, undated (Box 3, Folder 580)
  - Nickerson, Jane, undated (Box 3, Folder 581)
  - Nichols, Nell, undated (Box 3, Folder 582)
  - Nichols, Naomi, undated (Box 3, Folder 583)
  - Nidetch, Joan [Weight Watchers], undated (Box 3, Folder 584)
  - Niles, Bo, undated (Box 3, Folder 585)
  - Nilson, Bee, undated (Box 3, Folder 586)
  - Nimtz, Sharon, undated (Box 3, Folder 587)
  - Noble, Ruth, undated (Box 3, Folder 588)
  - Nye, Beverly, undated (Box 3, Folder 589)
  - O'Brien, Marian, undated (Box 3, Folder 590)
  - O'Connor, Hyla, undated (Box 3, Folder 591)
  - O'Donnell, Cornelius, undated (Box 3, Folder 592)
  - Ogiluy, Susan, undated (Box 3, Folder 593)
  - O'Hara, Nancy, undated (Box 3, Folder 594)
  - Ojakangas, Beatrice, undated (Box 3, Folder 595)
  - Olana State Historic Site, undated (Box 3, Folder 596)
  - Oliver, Sandra, undated (Box 3, Folder 597)
  - Olney, Richard, undated (Box 3, Folder 598)
  - Olson, Rik, undated (Box 3, Folder 599)
  - The 1006 Summit Avenue, undated (Box 3, Folder 600)
  - O'Neill, Molly, undated (Box 3, Folder 601)
  - Ottier, Sharon, undated (Box 3, Folder 602)
  - Paddleford, Clementine, undated (Box 3, Folder 603)
  - Papashvily, George, undated (Box 3, Folder 604)
  - Pappas, Lou, undated (Box 3, Folder 605)
  - Parker, Elinor, undated (Box 3, Folder 606)
  - Parker, Robert, undated (Box 3, Folder 607)
  - Parkill, Joe, undated (Box 3, Folder 608)
  - Parkin, Sue, undated (Box 3, Folder 609)
  - Parks, Lillian, undated (Box 3, Folder 610)
  - Parloa, Maria, undated (Box 3, Folder 611)
  - Pasley, Virginia, undated (Box 3, Folder 612)
  - Patterson, Evelyn, undated (Box 3, Folder 613)
  - Patti, Charles, undated (Box 3, Folder 614)
  - Paul, Florrie, undated (Box 3, Folder 615)
  - Pearson, Leonard and Lillian, undated (Box 3, Folder 616)
  - Peltz, Edith, undated (Box 3, Folder 617)
  - Penn, William, undated (Box 3, Folder 618)
  - Penner, Lucille, undated (Box 3, Folder 619)
  - Pennington, Kathryne, undated (Box 3, Folder 620)
  - Pápin, Jacques, undated (Box 3, Folder 621)
  - Pereira, Sue, undated (Box 3, Folder 622)
  - Perry, Ruth and Milton, undated (Box 3, Folder 623)
  - Peterson, Svein [Mrs.], undated (Box 3, Folder 624)
  - Petrova, Nina, undated (Box 3, Folder 625)
  - Pfeiffer, Carl and Jane Banks, undated (Box 3, Folder 626)
  - Philbin, Regis and Kathie Lee Gifford, undated (Box 3, Folder 627)
  - Pierce, Charles, undated (Box 3, Folder 628)
  - Pierce, Donn, undated (Box 3, Folder 629)
  - Piercy, Caroline and Arthur Tolve, undated (Box 3, Folder 630)
  - Pines, Jamie and Jennifer, undated (Box 3, Folder 631)
  - Pitts, Zasu, undated (Box 3, Folder 632)
  - Plagemann, Catherine, undated (Box 3, Folder 633)
  - Platt, June, undated (Box 3, Folder 634)
  - Polin, Bonnie and Frances Giedt, undated (Box 3, Folder 635)
  - Pomeroy, Ralph, undated (Box 3, Folder 636)
  - Porter, Sylvia, undated (Box 3, Folder 637)
  - Post, Emily, undated (Box 3, Folder 638)
  - Prada, Beatriz-Maria, undated (Box 3, Folder 639)
  - Pratt, Fletcher, undated (Box 3, Folder 640)
  - Pratt, James, undated (Box 3, Folder 641)
  - Prescott, Eileen, undated (Box 3, Folder 642)
  - Pressman, Thelma, undated (Box 3, Folder 643)
  - Price, Vincent and Mary, undated (Box 3, Folder 644)
  - Prichard, Anita, undated (Box 3, Folder 645)
  - Prince, Francine, undated (Box 3, Folder 646)
  - Princess, Pamela, undated (Box 3, Folder 647)
  - Pritikin, Nathan, undated (Box 3, Folder 648)
  - [Prosser], Tilghman, undated (Box 3, Folder 649)
  - Prunier, Simone, undated (Box 3, Folder 650)
  - Purdy, Susan, undated (Box 3, Folder 651)
  - Quan, Constance, undated (Box 3, Folder 652)
  - Quat, Helen, undated (Box 3, Folder 653)
  - Quattrociocchi, Niccolò de, undated (Box 3, Folder 654)
  - Rader, Barbara, undated (Box 3, Folder 655)
  - Raichlen, Steven, undated (Box 3, Folder 656)
  - Ralston, Nancy and Marynor Jordan, undated (Box 3, Folder 657)
  - Ramazani, Nesta, undated (Box 3, Folder 658)
  - Randolph, Mary, undated (Box 3, Folder 659)
  - Ranhofer, Charles, undated (Box 3, Folder 660)
  - Rankine, Susie, undated (Box 3, Folder 661)
  - Rapp, Joel, undated (Box 3, Folder 662)
  - Rattray, Jeanette, undated (Box 3, Folder 663)
  - Raup, Lucy, undated (Box 3, Folder 664)
  - Read, Jean and Mary Eckley, undated (Box 3, Folder 665)
  - Reboux, Paul, undated (Box 3, Folder 666)
  - Rechtschaffen, Joseph, undated (Box 3, Folder 667)
  - Redbook, undated (Box 3, Folder 668)
  - Reed, Ann and Marilyn Pfaltz, undated (Box 3, Folder 669)
  - Reed, Julia, undated (Box 3, Folder 670)
  - Reich, Lilly, undated (Box 3, Folder 671)
  - Reichl, Ruth, undated (Box 3, Folder 672)
  - Reinke, Judy, undated (Box 3, Folder 673)
  - Reuben, David and Barbara, undated (Box 3, Folder 674)
  - Rhoads, Sharon, undated (Box 3, Folder 675)
  - Rhode, Irma, undated (Box 3, Folder 676)
  - Riccio, Dolores, undated (Box 3, Folder 677)
  - Ridgeway, Arlene, undated (Box 3, Folder 678)
  - Ripperger, Helmut, undated (Box 3, Folder 679)
  - Riviere, Bill, undated (Box 3, Folder 680)
  - Robb, Phyllis, undated (Box 3, Folder 681)
  - Robbins, Ann, undated (Box 3, Folder 682)
  - Roberts, Susan and Melvin Heyman, undated (Box 3, Folder 683)
  - Robertson, Donald and Carol, undated (Box 3, Folder 684)
  - Rodale, Robert, undated (Box 3, Folder 685)
  - Roden, Claudia, undated (Box 3, Folder 686)
  - Rogers, Dorothy, undated (Box 3, Folder 687)
  - Rogers, Sheridan, undated (Box 3, Folder 688)
  - Rojas-Lombardi, Felipe, undated (Box 3, Folder 689)
  - Rombauer, Irma (correspondence), undated (Box 4, Folder 690)
  - Rombauer / Becker publicity, undated (Box 4, Folder 691)
  - Roosevelt, Belle, undated (Box 4, Folder 692)
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas, undated (Box 4, Folder 693)
  - Roper, Sarah Tyson, undated (Box 4, Folder 694)
  - Rorer, Saray, undated (Box 4, Folder 695)
  - Rosenbaum, Helen, undated (Box 4, Folder 696)
  - Rosenblatt, Julia and Frederic Sonnenschmidt, undated (Box 4, Folder 697)
  - Rosengarten, David, undated (Box 4, Folder 698)
  - Rosenthal, Barbara and Nadia, undated (Box 4, Folder 699)
  - Rosenthal, Sylvia, undated (Box 4, Folder 700)
  - Rosenthaler, E[lisabeth], undated (Box 4, Folder 701)
  - Ross, Elaine, undated (Box 4, Folder 702)
  - Ross, Pat, undated (Box 4, Folder 703)
  - Ross, Shirley, undated (Box 4, Folder 704)
  - Rossant, Colette, undated (Box 4, Folder 705)
  - Roth, Geneen, undated (Box 4, Folder 706)
  - Roth, June, undated (Box 4, Folder 707)
  - Roth, Sherrill and Gil, undated (Box 4, Folder 708)
  - Rubin, Charles et al, undated (Box 4, Folder 709)
  - Rubin, Eleanor, undated (Box 4, Folder 710)
  - Rubinstein, Paul, undated (Box 4, Folder 711)
  - Rundell, Mrs., undated (Box 4, Folder 712)
  - Rupprecht, Fred, undated (Box 4, Folder 713)
  - Russell, Maria and Maxine Stromberg, undated (Box 4, Folder 714)
  - Rutledge, Sarah, undated (Box 4, Folder 715)
  - Rywell, Martin, undated (Box 4, Folder 716)
  - Safford, Virginia, undated (Box 4, Folder 717)
  - Sagendorph, Robb, undated (Box 4, Folder 718)
  - Sailland, Maurice, undated (Box 4, Folder 719)
  - Saint-Ange, Madame, undated (Box 4, Folder 720)
  - Sala, George, undated (Box 4, Folder 721)
  - Sanders, Dori, undated (Box 4, Folder 722)
  - Sanderson, Jean, undated (Box 4, Folder 723)
  - Sandler, Bea, undated (Box 4, Folder 724)
  - Sardi, Eugenia and Vincent, undated (Box 4, Folder 725)
  - Sass, Lorna, undated (Box 4, Folder 726)
  - Saunders, Caryl, undated (Box 4, Folder 727)
  - Schafer, Violet, undated (Box 4, Folder 728)
  - Schell, Merle, undated (Box 4, Folder 729)
  - Schioler, Gail, undated (Box 4, Folder 730)
  - Schmidt, William, undated (Box 4, Folder 731)
  - Schneider, Carol, undated (Box 4, Folder 732)
  - Schnuelle, Leona, undated (Box 4, Folder 733)
  - Schryver, Elliott, undated (Box 4, Folder 734)
  - Schulz, Charles, undated (Box 4, Folder 735)
  - Schultz, Sigrid, undated (Box 4, Folder 736)
  - Schwartz, Alvin, undated (Box 4, Folder 737)
  - Scott, Jack and Maria, undated (Box 4, Folder 738)
  - Selden, Gary, undated (Box 4, Folder 739)
  - Sell, Henry, undated (Box 4, Folder 740)
  - Senderens, Alain, undated (Box 4, Folder 741)
  - Seranne, Ann, undated (Box 4, Folder 742)
  - Servaas, Cory and Walter Mathews, undated (Box 4, Folder 743)
  - Selter, Faye, undated (Box 4, Folder 744)
  - Sewell, Thelma, undated (Box 4, Folder 745)
  - Sheedy, Charlotte and Norman Keifetz, undated (Box 4, Folder 746)
  - Sheridan, Monica, undated (Box 4, Folder 747)
  - Sherman, Steve, undated (Box 4, Folder 748)
  - Shimizu, Kay, undated (Box 4, Folder 749)
  - Shosteck, Patti, undated (Box 4, Folder 750)
  - Shulman, Martha, undated (Box 4, Folder 751)
  - Shurtleff, William and Akiko, undated (Box 4, Folder 752)
  - Siegal, Sanford, undated (Box 4, Folder 753)
  - Sieveling, Earle, undated (Box 4, Folder 754)
  - Simeti, Mary, undated (Box 4, Folder 755)
  - Simmons, Amelia, undated (Box 4, Folder 756)
  - Simon, Andrá and Robin Howe, undated (Box 4, Folder 757)
  - [Simonds], Nina, undated (Box 4, Folder 758)
  - Sims, Dorthy, undated (Box 4, Folder 759)
  - Singer, Myrtle, undated (Box 4, Folder 760)
  - Six-Sided Nickel, undated (Box 4, Folder 761)
  - Slezak, Walter, undated (Box 4, Folder 762)
  - Smith, Andrew, undated (Box 4, Folder 763)
  - Smith, Lendon, undated (Box 4, Folder 764)
  - Smith, Libby, undated (Box 4, Folder 765)
  - Smith, Myrtle, undated (Box 4, Folder 766)
  - Smith, Ralph, undated (Box 4, Folder 767)
  - Snyder, Jerome, undated (Box 4, Folder 768)
  - Sokolov, Raymond, undated (Box 4, Folder 769)
  - Sondheimer, Carl, undated (Box 4, Folder 770)
  - Sourdough Jack, undated (Box 4, Folder 771)
  - Southern Living, undated (Box 4, Folder 772)
  - Soyer, Alexis, undated (Box 4, Folder 773)
  - Spear, Ruth, undated (Box 4, Folder 774)
  - Sprackling, Helen, undated (Box 4, Folder 775)
  - Spry, Constance, undated (Box 4, Folder 776)
  - Standard, Stella, undated (Box 4, Folder 777)
  - Stapleton, Katie, undated (Box 4, Folder 778)
  - Stead, Evelyn and Gloria Warren, undated (Box 4, Folder 779)
  - Stegner, Mabel, undated (Box 4, Folder 780)
  - Steinberg, Rafael, undated (Box 4, Folder 781)
  - Steorts, Nancy, undated (Box 4, Folder 782)
  - Stillman, Joan, undated (Box 4, Folder 783)
  - Stone, [___], undated (Box 4, Folder 784)
  - Stoner, Carol, undated (Box 4, Folder 785)
  - Storm, John and Margaret, undated (Box 4, Folder 786)
  - Stout, Rex, undated (Box 4, Folder 787)
  - Stout, Ruth, undated (Box 4, Folder 788)
  - Stovel, Edith, undated (Box 4, Folder 789)
  - Stover, Annette, undated (Box 4, Folder 790)
  - Stover, Blanche, undated (Box 4, Folder 791)
  - Stowe, Harriet Beecher, undated (Box 4, Folder 792)
  - Straus, Roger, undated (Box 4, Folder 793)
  - Stubbs, Jane, undated (Box 4, Folder 794)
  - Stuckey, Lillie and Avanelle Day, undated (Box 4, Folder 795)
  - Sullivan, Lenore, undated (Box 4, Folder 796)
  - Sunkist, undated (Box 4, Folder 797)
  - Sunset Books, undated (Box 4, Folder 798)
  - Surmaine, Andre, undated (Box 4, Folder 799)
  - Swanson, Ruby, undated (Box 4, Folder 800)
  - Szathmary, Louis, undated (Box 4, Folder 800 A)
  - Taber, Gladys, undated (Box 4, Folder 801)
  - Taeuber, Dick, undated (Box 4, Folder 802)
  - Tai, Pauline, undated (Box 4, Folder 803)
  - Talmadge, Herman, undated (Box 4, Folder 804)
  - Tarr, Yvonne, undated (Box 4, Folder 805)
  - Tartan, Beth, undated (Box 4, Folder 806)
  - Tatum, Billy Joe, undated (Box 4, Folder 807)
  - Taylor, Diane, undated (Box 4, Folder 808)
  - Taylor, John [Hoppin' John], undated (Box 4, Folder 809)
  - Teague, Ruth, undated (Box 4, Folder 810)